# Ganzorig Erdenebat

Address: Miami, FL https://rozig.me Mobile: +1 (312) 404-1266

Email: the.ganzorig25@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/rozig/

### Summary

Accomplished full-stack developer with over 2 years of experience playing key role in design, development, deployment, and support of enterprise-level software. Strong technical skills, with hands-on experience in both front-end and back- end development using Django and Angular web frameworks. Personable team player with talent for collaborating with diverse technical teams. Experience successfully implementing projects with web services, design patterns and latest frameworks.

### **EDUCATION**

## Maharishi University of Management

Fairfield, IA

Master of Science in Computer Science; GPA: 3.90

Oct. 2017 - Present

Mongolian University of Science and Technology

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia Aug. 2013 - Jan. 2017

Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering; GPA: 3.46

#### EXPERIENCE

Genius Plaza Inc.

Miami, FL

Aug. 2018 - Present

- Genius Plaza: RESTful API development on Django and DjangoREST Framework.
- Genius Baby: Created database design and system architecture. Works on development and deployment.

# Infinite Solutions LLC

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

Full Stack Developer

Back-end Developer

Jun. 2016 - Nov. 2017

- o Transfer: Transfer is a fintech solution for receiving and sending money over the world. Worked on core system, API services and front-end development.
- o Mobicom Branded Application: Managed back-end server for Mobicom Branded Application. Performed backend development, API services development, testing and maintenance and database design.
- o Golds Gym Website: Developed official website for Golds Gym Mongolia. Conducted unit testing and maintenance. Performed front-end and back-end development.
- ArigBank: In-charge of maintenance and front-end development.

#### Projects

- React.js boilerplate: Boilerplate project for React.js. Used webpack, styled-components and react-router.
- Online Publication Platform: Clone of Medium.com, built RESTful API and implemented JWT authentication.
- Mumagram: Instagram-like social networking web application for MUM students.
- MUMSched: Academic scheduling web application for MUM students.
- Online Banking Application: Web application that allows user to transfer money and manage their accounts.
- Nutrition Calculator: Nutrition calculator web application on Django (Python).
- Logistics System: Web application for cargo delivery on Django (Python).

#### Programming Skills

• Languages: Python, PHP, JavaScript, TypeScript, Bash, SQL SDLC: Agile/SCRUM, RUP, Waterfall

• Web: ¡Query, CSS3/HTML5, SASS, Express Frameworks: Django, Symfony, NodeJS, Angular 2/4/5

• Web/App Servers: Nginx, Apache2, Node Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, SQLAlchemy

• Design Patterns: Factory Method, Singleton, Adapter, MVC Web Services: RESTful, Django REST

• Tools: Git, Vim, Terminal, AWS, Google Cloud Platform, Bash, zsh Platforms: UNIX/Linux, Windows